<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blogs | KinGBin Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/blog/categories/blogs/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-05-02T20:44:33-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://kingbin.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Chris Blazek]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[hard to walk away]]></title>
    <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2013/05/02/hard-to-walk-away/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-02T19:43:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2013/05/02/hard-to-walk-away</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>It's HARD to walk away some days</h3>

<p>I've been training for triathlons and I started out following a plan from active.com. Specifically training for an Olympic length in June. I've been putting in more miles than the plan requires, doing what I feel is comfortable 6 days a week. I am getting a ton of miles in a week over swim/bike/run. I am doing activities that I LOVE and I want more!</p>


<p> I signed up for my first tri this weekend. I'm a little (my wife would say very) anxious for the race. I'm not really competitive with other individuals but more for just setting goals for myself. This is my journey to hopefully a 1/2 IM. I've got my wetsuit and gear all prepped. I need to switch out my training tire on the bike after I do one more practive ride (It's freezing 30+ mph winds!). I swam 2 1k drills last night. I've got my hammer supplements ready. The swim will start out in the 40's and by the time bike/run rolls around, it should be in the mid 50's.</p>


<p>I have learned so much about myself and life by participating in these events. I feel at peace with everything in my life as I spend my time training for these events. I can feel God right beside me every mile of the journey. I have learned that I'm not in control, the only thing I do have control of is to keep moving forward through the glory & pain. I can't wait for my boys to experience this high with me.</p>


<p>In two weeks I'll be down in Blanco for a bike race. I can't wait to meet up with an old high school friend to tackle the hills. Another experience I'm greatful to enjoy.</p>


<p>I've been really excited about work. A couple weeks ago I was moved to the team that works on web & mobile development. In a given day I'll work on node/javascript/ember mvc/c++ wrappers/ruby/c#/pascal. I've been working on a solution to hotload resources to clients through javascript libraries. I've got a rock solid bower server implemented with oauth & a start to websockets for updates. I'm excited where the projects are going and it's hard to break away for lunch. I wake up in the morning with a ton of things I want to get done and I can't wait to get started.</p>


<br/><p>Life is good!</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Switch Or Not]]></title>
    <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/to-switch-or-not/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-08T11:05:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/to-switch-or-not</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p></p>

<p>I'm testing octopress &amp; github's pages hosting..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
