<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: daily | KinGBin Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/blog/categories/daily/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-23T14:07:47-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://kingbin.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Chris Blazek]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cats Meow]]></title>
    <link href="http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2012/12/23/cats/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-23T13:48:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://kingbin.github.com/blog/2012/12/23/cats</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://placekitten.com/890/280"></p>

<p>Well this is a fun new adventure for my blog.</p>

<p>It's moved from blogger.com to a locally hosted site, then to a local wordress install and now gh-pages.</p>

<p>I haven't migrated the old content and I'm not sure I will. I moved to ghpages because my new provider blocks port 80. I was told that port was for nothing but malicious intents.</p>

<p>This new format allows me to use rake commands to generate new posts, test and deploy along with ties to github. I appreciate the approach because it allows me to work in the tools I would spend all day in if I could. I'm using erb templates and other slick plugins that make sense to me as a developer.</p>

<p>I need to figure out how I want to handle some of the little development I did at the house. I went to dyndns and you have to now pay for the service. I believe you can cancel the trial and still be limited to one host. Which will work for what I want to do. I still need to setup the CNAME aliases to point to different services I run at the house.</p>

<p>Probably the best part about all this is that I'm using VI to create posts.</p>

<p>File /Users/chrisblazek/Documents/Development/Websites/octopress/source/downloads/code/coffeescript/fib.coffee could not be found</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
